Alright, for indoor and outdoor hockey, roller hockey, you need a ball for outdoor and for indoor you would want to use a specified roller hockey puck.
They sell them to, they'll sell them to any sporting goods store would have them.
You can go there and check it out and they can tell you which ones are the best ones or whatever.
Basically a roller hockey puck is basically the same size as a regular ice hockey puck.
It would be a little bit lighter.
It's made of plastic.
But at the pro shop they would be able to explain it a little bit better, and you can check it out.
See if you want to get one of those.
If you need it or whatever.
You can use them outdoor too if you want.
It just doesn't work very well if you have a lot of cracks, stuff like that.
The puck will be bouncing around.
So typically outdoors what you want is just a roller hockey ball.
It just works good rolling around out here.
You can stick handle really good with it.
And it works great.
So, use that.